(Sheldon:)A, I rarely kid.
(Sheldon:)And B, when I do kid, you will know it
by my use of the word "buzzinga."
(Howard:)So you're saying the two of you are
going to be sleeping in the same bed?
(Howard:)Yes.
Buzzinga.
(Sheldon:)Leonard?
(Leonard:)Thank you.
Why is a renowned scientist staying
in our apartment instead of a hotel?
(Sheldon:)She doesn't care for hotels.
And who can blame her?
(Sheldon:)Windows that don't open,
multi-user linens...
(Sheldon:)...keys shaped like credit cards.
(Sheldon:)As if one walks around
with unassigned slots in one's wallet.
(Sheldon:)All right, I believe I have time
for one more question.
[RAJESH CLEARS THROAT]
(Sheldon:)Yes, Raj?
RAJESH:
When can I sit with you again?
When I've seen two negative
throat cultures spaced 12 hours apart.
(Sheldon:)You know the drill.
(Sheldon:)All right, if you'll excuse me...
(Sheldon:)...I am off to start
a prophylactic course of antibiotics.
(Leonard:)I can't believe he's friends
with Elizabeth Plimpton.
(Leonard:)I can't believe
they let him into Canada.
(Howard:)Whoa. You heard the man.
Where's your throat cultures?
(Howard:)-Kidding. Sit down.
LEONARD: Ha.
[SNEEZES]